(Raj:)-Why didn't you say anything?
-I was waiting for the right time.
(Howard:)This is the right time.
Hey, who's ready for "Halo"?
(Raj:)Oh, this is like a nightmare. Get lost.
(Howard:)The numbers
are shaky enough as it is.
(Leonard:)I don't understand.
(Elizabeth:)Oh, good. Leonard's here.
(Raj:)Good?
(Leonard:)Elizabeth? What's going on?
(Elizabeth:)What's going on is you and Howard
are my moving men.
(Elizabeth:)And Raj is my new landlord.
(Elizabeth:)And I don't have enough money
to pay any of you.
(Leonard:)Is she suggesting
what I think she's suggesting?
Yup. Welcome to
the Penthouse Forum.
(Raj:)Okay, show of hands.
Who's up for this?
(Leonard:)We'll all be naked
in front of each other.
(Howard:)I'm out.
(Elizabeth:)Everybody ready?
(Raj:)Follow my lead. Almost.
(Raj:)We're going to go out into the hallway
and make a dramatic entrance.
(Elizabeth:)Oh, good. It's so much better
when everyone commits.